Guide to the War Poster Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- World War I, 1914-1918; Series I
  - Lafon Allen Collection
    - France
      - Pour la Lorraine Liberee: Ses Ministres; Ses Soldats, 1918 December; AFR0340; 24x31 inches (Box 27)
      - Souvons les Bebes, 1917 December; AFR0341; 24x31 inches (Box 27)
        Artist: Stephanu. Place of Publication: France.
      - Le Village Reconstitue, 1918; AFR0342; 46x32 inches (Box 27)
        Artist: Cappielo. Place of Publication: France.
      - 1918. Journee Rouennaise des Oeuvres de Guerre, 1918 April; AFR0343; 23x14 inches (Box 27)
        Artist: Felt, Julien. Place of Publication: France.
      - Vile de Toulouse. Comite Central des Oeuvres de Guerre, 1917; AFR0344; 47x31 inches (Box 27)
        Artist: Auglay. Place of Publication: France.
      - Orphelinat des Armees, 1916; AFR0345; 40x60 inches (Box 27)
        Artist: Brangwyn, Frank. Place of Publication: France.
      - Le Pas-de-Calais Devaste, 1919 May; AFR0346; 30x22 inches (Box 27)
      - 18 Aout 1918. 4me. Journee du Calvados, 1918 August; AFR0347; 25x37 inches (Box 27)
      - Semaine d'Economies et de Charite, 1917 December; AFR0348; 34x48 inches (Box 27)
        Artist: Barber. Place of Publication: France.
      - Republique Francaise. Journee du 75, Dimanche, 1915 January 16; AFR0349; 22x30 inches (Box 27)
      - La France Pressera sur son coeur ses Fils qui l'Auront Sauvee., 1918; AFR0350; 47x31 inches (Box 27)
      - Societe Francaise de Secours aux Blesses Militaires, 1914; AFR0351; 26x31 inches (Box 28)
      - Exposition de L'Enfance Organisee par la Croix Rouge Americaine, 1918 September 30; AFR0352; 31x47 inches (Box 28)
        Artist: Schamdandjian. Place of Publication: France.
      - Societe Protectrice de L'Enfance, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0354; 41x78 inches (Box 28)
        Artist: Georges. Place of Publication: France.
      - Journee des Regions Liberees, 1919 July 14; AFR0355; 31x47 inches (Box 28)
      - Journee des Regions Liberees, 1919 July 14; AFR0356; 31x47 inches (Box 28)
      - Journee des Regions Liberees, 1919 July 14; AFR0357; 31x47 inches (Box 28)
        Artist: LeRoux, Auguste. Place of Publication: France.
      - En l'Hotel Murat; Vente de Charite, 1919 June; AFR0358; 23.5x31.5 inches (Box 28)
      - Le Retour au Foyer, 1917 October; AFR0359; 31x47 inches (Box 28)
      - Oeuvre du Soldat Ardennais., 1916; AFR0360; 24x35 inches (Box 28)
        Artist: Breval, Roger. Place of Publication: France.
      - Orphelinat des Armees., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0361; 32x46 inches (Box 28)
      - Orphelinat des Armees; Journee du let. Riem., 1917; AFR0362; 36x26 inches (Box 28)
        Artist: Riem. Place of Publication: France.
      - 20,000 Alsciens-Loraine, engages Volontaires, 1917 November; AFR0363; 47x31 inches (Box 28)
      - La Renaissance des Foyers en Alsace, 1915; AFR0364; 31x46 inches (Box 28)
        Artist: Benner, May. Place of Publication: France.
      - Journee de l'Anjou; Dimanche 17 Juin, 1917., AFR0365; 31x47 inches (Box 28)
      - Exposition; Petit Palais, 1918; AFR0366; 24x31 inches (Box 28)
        Artist: Boignard, Camille. Place of Publication: France.
      - Oeuvre du Soldat Belge, 1915; AFR0367; 20x30 inches (Box 28)
      - La Journee Serbe: 25 Juin 1916: Anniversaire, 1916 June; AFR0368; 48x32 inches (Box 29)
      - 26 Juin 1916: Journee Serbe., 1916 June; AFR0369; 32x48 inches (Box 29)
      - Journee Serbe, 25 Juin 1916., 1916 June; AFR0370; 48x32 inches (Box 29)
        Artist: Mourgue. Place of Publication: France.
      - Sur le Terre Ennemie les Prisonniers Russe Meurent de Faim., 1917; AFR0371; 31x45 inches (Box 29)
      - Journee Serbe, 1916 June 25; AFR0372; 30x44 inches (Box 29)
      - Exposition des Photographies Officielles L'Armee Canadienne, 1917 December; AFR0373; 22x30 inches (Box 29)
      - Theatre du Chatelet. Gala de Musique Romaine, 1917 May; AFR0374; 40x56 inches (Box 29)
      - Tous les Petits Pour les Petits, 1916 March 30; AFR0375; 47x32 inches (Box 29)
      - Concert et Exposition Serbe, 1916 June; AFR0376; 32x47 inches (Box 29)
        Artist: Vorkapitch. Place of Publication: France.
      - Exposition d'Art Marocain, 1917; AFR0377; 28x38 inches (Box 29)
        Artist: Rabot. (Sela Neziere). Place of Publication: France.
      - Comite de Secours Aux Refugies Serbes, 1918 December; AFR0378; 48x32 inches (Box 29)
      - Exposition Franco-Polonaise, 1919 March; AFR0379; 24x31 inches (Box 29)
        Artist: Burke, Boleslus. Place of Publication: France.
      - Noel, 1918. Fete d'Arbre de Noel., 1918 December; AFR0380; 21x32 inches (Box 29)
        Artist: Sarasin, Regnault. Place of Publication: France.
      - Comite General de Secours aux Victimes de la Guerre en Pologne, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0381; 20x30 inches (Box 29)
      - A la France Ouvriere et Paysanne! Aux Travalleurs de Paris, 1918; AFR0382; 24x32 inches (Box 30)
      - Vive Willson!, 1918; AFR0383; 24x31 inches (Box 30)
      - A Tous les Francais, 1918; AFR0384; 24x31 inches (Box 30)
      - La Ligue des Familles Nombreuses de France et les Conditions, 1918; AFR0385; 24x31 inches (Box 30)
      - Appeal a l'Opinion. Manifeste de la Ligue Maritime Francaise, 1919; AFR0386; 24x31 inches (Box 30)
      - La Fontaine l'Avait Bien Dit!, 1918 October; AFR0387; 12x22 inches (Box 30)
        Artist: Morin, Louis. Place of Publication: France.
      - Passant, Qui Devant Moi t'arretes, 1918; AFR0388; 15x20 inches (Box 30)
      - Passant, Qui Devant Moi t'arretes, 1918; AFR0389; 15x20 inches (Box 30)
      - Il Faut Vaincre la Tuberculose Comme la Plus Malfaisant, 1918; AFR0390; 30x46 inches (Box 30)
      - Le Plege. Francais! Sous les Coups de Nos Poilus, le Trone, 1918 October 9; AFR0391; 25x30 inches (Box 30)
      - Noel pour la Grande Paix qui Vient, 1918; AFR0392; 22x30 inches (Box 30)
      - Comment Ils Ecrivent l'Histoire, 1918; AFR0393; 22x30 inches (Box 30)
      - La Marseillaise, 1918 December; AFR0394; 31x47 inches (Box 30)
      - La Victoire en Chantant, 1918; AFR0395; 22x30 inches (Box 30)
      - Aux Camarades Ouvriers et Employes, 1918 August; AFR0396; 24x31 inches (Box 30)
      - Deux Coeurs Fideles qui Ont Souffert sous la Jouq Allemand, 1918; AFR0397; 24x31 inches (Box 30)
      - En Alsace Liberee, 1918; AFR0398; 15x22 inches (Box 30)
        Artist: Groqnuz, Beatrix. Place of Publication: France.
      - Conferences de la Revue des Jeunes. L'Utilization de la Victoire, 1919 January; AFR0399; 21x47 inches (Box 30)
      - Francais! N'Oubliez pas qu'en Aout 1914, 1916 December; AFR0400; 16x23 inches (Box 30)
      - Francais! Pour nous Revitailler, les Americains se Rationnent, 1918 February; AFR0401; 24x16 inches (Box 31)
      - Appel aux Pouvoirs Publics et aux Citoyens Francais, 1918 April; AFR0402; 24x32 inches (Box 31)
      - Parisiens, 1918 March; AFR0403; 35x31 inches (Box 31)
      - Bien-Etre et Liberte!, 1918 April; AFR0404; 25x34 inches (Box 31)
      - Ligue Civique. De Nouvelles Restrictions Alimentaires, 1918 May; AFR0405; 25x34 inches (Box 31)
      - Attention aux Futurs Echanges de Prisonniers Allemands!, 1918 May; AFR0406; 36x25 inches (Box 31)
      - Au Peuple de France, 1918 June; AFR0407; 25x33 inches (Box 31)
      - Par la Victoire vers la Paix du Droit avec le President Wilson, 1918; AFR0408; 25x32 inches (Box 31)
      - Les Alsaciens-Lorrains sont nos Freres, 1918; AFR0409; 23x35 inches (Box 31)
      - A la Nation Francais, 1918; AFR0410; 24x32 inches (Box 31)
      - On ne Peut pas Servir l'Humanite aux Depens de la France, 1918 July; AFR0411; 19x12 inches (Box 31)
      - Francais! Souvenez-vous de ce que les Boches ont fait a Luneville, 1918 July; AFR0412; 23x31 inches (Box 31)
      - Francais! N'Oubliez pas les Martyres de Lille Assassines, 1918 July; AFR0413; 24x32 inches (Box 31)
      - A tous les Francais, 1918; AFR0414; 24x31 inches (Box 31)
      - Alliance Universitaire Francaise. Vigilance et Souvenir, 1918; AFR0415; 22x30 inches (Box 31)
      - La Voix des Grands Tribuns du Peuple, 1918 February 20; AFR0416; 20x26 inches (Box 31)
      - Grande Manifestation Nationale, 1919 April; AFR0417; 23x31 inches (Box 31)
      - Per deux fois j'ai tenu et vaincu sur la Marne, 1918; AFR0418; 16x23 inches (Box 31)
      - Le Droit, La Liberte, 1918 September; AFR0419; 21x28 inches (Box 31)
      - Alliance Universitaire. Le Dilemme pour la France, vaincre, 1918 August 29; AFR0420; 22x14 inches (Box 31)
      - A la Gloire de Jean Corventin Carre, 1918; AFR0421; 24x30 inches (Box 31)
      - Navires-Hopitaux Torpilles par les Allemands, 1917; AFR0422; 24x31 inches (Box 31)
      - Les Preliminaires de la Paix, 1919; AFR0423; 28x30 inches (Box 31)
      - L'Amerique lutte pour l'Independence des Deux Mondes, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0424; 19x24 inches (Box 31)
      - Le Laboratoire; L'Usine; La Guerre, 1918; AFR0425; 19x25 inches (Box 31)
      - L'Effort Paysan., 1918; AFR0426; 20x26 inches (Box 31)
      - L'Ideal Moral et l'Ecole, 1919; AFR0427; 24x31 inches (Box 31)
      - Appel du Ministre de l'Instruction Publique et des Beaux-Arts, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0428; 15x24 inches (Box 31)
      - Semez des Pommes de Terre, 1917 March 31; AFR0429; 29x41 inches (Box 32)
        Artist: Hautot. Place of Publication: France.
      - Hygiene de Guerre, 1917; AFR0430; 20x25 inches (Box 32)
      - Ne pas Gaspiller le Pain est Notre Devoir, 1918; AFR0431; 14x21 inches (Box 32)
      - Terre cultivee, terre nourriciere, 1917; AFR0432; 19x25 inches (Box 32)
      - Nous Saurons, Nous en Priver, 1918; AFR0433; 14x22 inches (Box 32)
        Artist: Boutet, Camille. Place of Publication: France.
      - Economisons le pain en mangent des pommes de terre., 1918; AFR0434; 15x22 inches (Box 32)
      - Mangeez Moins de Viande pour Menager Notre Cheptel., 1918; AFR0435; 15x22 inches (Box 32)
      - Il faut produire, 1917; AFR0436; 18x25 inches (Box 32)
      - Extrait du Journal Officiel du 26 Janvier, 1917, Arrete, 1917 January 26; AFR0437; 09x11 inches (Box 32)
      - Semez duble; c'est de l'or pour la France., 1918; AFR0438; 14x22 inches (Box 32)
        Artist: Ferrand, Suzanne. Place of Publication: France.
      - Semez du Ble!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0439; 22x29 inches (Box 32)
      - Economisons le Petrole, L'Essence., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0440; 15x22 inches (Box 32)
        Artist: Jeanningros, Marie. Place of Publication: France.
      - Avec la Carte, Nous on Aurons peu, mais nous en Aurons tous, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0441; 14x31 inches (Box 32)
        Artist: Colas, Yvonne. Place of Publication: France.
      - Francais, Economisez le Gaz., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0442; 14x22 inches (Box 32)
        Artist: Falborroux, Jeanne. Place of Publication: France.
      - Silence! Ne Parlez pas de la Guerre: Nos Emmenis Vous, 1917; AFR0443; 10x08 inches (Box 33)
      - 1776-1917, AFR0444; 38x48 inches (Box 33)
        Artist: Buthaud, R. Place of Publication: France.
      - Ah! Quand Supprimera-t-on l'Alcool?, 1917 August; AFR0445; 31x47 inches (Box 33)
      - Souvenez-vous des crimes allemands; Gerbeviller, 1914, 1917 October 20; AFR0446; 31x47 inches (Box 33)
        Artist: Berrere, A.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Souvenez-Vous!, 1917 October 30; AFR0447; 31x47 inches (Box 33)
        Artist: Jonas, Ch.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Jonas, Lucien-Hector, 1917 October 30; AFR0448; 31x47 inches (Box 33)
        Artist: Exposition. Place of Publication: France.
      - Soldat! La Patrie Compte sur toi; Garde lui Toutes des Forces, 1916; AFR0449; 24x31 inches (Box 33)
      - Aux Travailleurs de la Defense Nationale, 1918; AFR0450; 30x22 inches (Box 33)
      - Qui Veut l'Allemagne?, 1917; AFR0451; 20x24 inches (Box 33)
      - Le passe de la Prusse, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0452; 20x24 inches (Box 33)
      - La Paix de l'Ennemi, 1917; AFR0453; 20x25 inches (Box 33)
      - La Voix des Ruines, 1917; AFR0454; 24x20 inches (Box 33)
      - Debout nos Morts pour la Patrie, 1918; AFR0455; 22x18 inches (Box 33)
      - Les Alsaciens et les Lorrains sont Francais., 1918; AFR0456; 18x29 inches (Box 33)
      - Viola les Americains, 1917; AFR0457; 25x20 inches (Box 33)
        Artist: Sounier. Place of Publication: France.
      - Pour la Liberte: Fete de l'Independence, 1918 July; AFR0458; 13x19 inches (Box 33)
        Artist: Benito. Place of Publication: France.
      - L'Accueil de la Suisse aux Rapatries, 1917; AFR0459; 20x26 inches (Box 33)
      - Retour de Captivite des Officiers et Hommes du Troupe, 1918 May; AFR0460; 23x16 inches (Box 33)
      - Le Bonnet Rouge, Circa 1916 - circa 1917; AFR0461; 31x24 inches (Box 33)
      - Toute la France Debout pour la Victoire du Droit aux Agriculteurs, 1918; AFR0462; 16x23 inches (Box 33)
      - En 1788 Mirabeau disait deja la Guerre est l'Industrie, 1918; AFR0463; 31x23 inches (Box 33)
      - Preparation de la Jeunesse Francais au Sevice Militaire., 1918; AFR0464; 32x48 inches (Box 34)
      - L'Aurore., 1918 July 25; AFR0465; 24x32 inches (Box 34)
      - Les Nationalite Opprimees., 1917; AFR0466; 18x25 inches (Box 34)
      - Ce que nous Devons a nos Colonies, 1917; AFR0467; 18x25 inches (Box 34)
      - L'Effort Maritime, 1917; AFR0468; 18x25 inches (Box 34)
      - Soyez Patients; Soyez Obstines, 1917; AFR0469; 18x25 inches (Box 34)
      - Les Combattants de la Grande Guerre., 1918; AFR0470; 23x32 inches (Box 34)
        Artist: Carrey. Place of Publication: France.
      - Les Combattants de la Grande Guerre., 1918; AFR0471; 23x32 inches (Box 34)
      - La Ruee en 1914, 1917; AFR0472; 18x25 inches (Box 34)
      - Le Pays, 1917; AFR0473; 47x64 inches (Box 34)
      - Le Respect des Droits de l'Homme Garantit la Paix du Monde., 1918 february; AFR0474; 20x26 inches (Box 34)
      - La France Libre, 1918; AFR0475; 32x47 inches (Box 34)
        Artist: Reni-Mel. Place of Publication: France.
      - Souvenez-Vous., 1917; AFR0476; 13x22 inches (Box 34)
        Artist: Gottlob, Ferdinand Louis. Place of Publication: France.
      - Pourquoi la Paix ne Peut-Etre Fondee sur la Parole de l'Allemagne., 1918 February; AFR0477; 44x30 inches (Box 34)
      - Pour la Liberte du Monde., 1918; AFR0478; 31x46 inches (Box 34)
        Artist: Vion, Raoul. Place of Publication: France.
      - Ah! Si l'On Avait Supprime l'Alcool, 1918 March; AFR0479; 32x47 inches (Box 34)
      - Ah! Si l'On Avait Supprime l'Alcool, 1919 January; AFR0480; 32x47 inches (Box 34)
      - Par Deux Fois J'ai Tenu et Vaincu Sur la Marne, 1918; AFR0481; 32x47 inches (Box 34)
      - Pressant Apel a la Solidarite, 1916; AFR0482; 43x54 inches (Box 34)
        Artist: Tinayre, Louis. Place of Publication: France.
      - L'Effort et l'Ideal de la Grande Bretagne, 1918 February; AFR0483; 24x33 inches (Box 35)
      - Souvenez-Vous! 1914, 1915 January; AFR0484; 24x33 inches (Box 35)
        Artist: Lemeille. Place of Publication: France.
      - La Democratic Nouvella, 1918 September; AFR0485; 32x41 inches (Box 35)
        Artist: Patricot. Place of Publication: France.
      - Souvenez-Vous? N'Oubliez Jamais les Crimes Allemands, 1918; AFR0486; 26x40 inches (Box 35)
      - La Culture des Peuples Revele par Leur Conception du Droit, 1918 February; AFR0487; 20x26 inches (Box 35)
      - Le Grand Etatmajour Allemand Avait Promedite Ses Atrocites, 1918 February; AFR0488; 19x26 inches (Box 35)
      - La Liberte ou l'Esclavage, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0489; 20x26 inches (Box 35)
      - En Peuple est Devanu par son Orgueil l'Eternelle Menace, 1918 February; AFR0490; 20x26 inches (Box 35)
      - Le Plan Pangermaniste, 1918 February; AFR0491; 20x26 inches (Box 35)
      - Pourquoi la Paix ne Peut Etre Basee que sur la Victoire, 1918 February; AFR0492; 19x26 inches (Box 35)
      - L'Allemagne a Provoque la Guerre., 1918 February; AFR0493; 19x26 inches (Box 35)
      - La Volonte d'Agression de l'Allemane, 1918 February; AFR0494; 20x26 inches (Box 35)
      - Francais - Ne Vous Installez Pas...Taisons Nous, 1916 December; AFR0495; 13x20 inches (Box 35)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: France. 3 separate posters.
      - Commemoration, La Protection des Deputes de l'Alsace et de la, 1918; AFR0496; inches (Box 35)
      - Declaration des Deputes d'Alsace-Lorraine, 1918; AFR0497; 18x30 inches (Box 35)
      - Declaration des Deputes d'Alsace-Lorraine, 1918; AFR0498; 30x22 inches (Box 35)
        Artist: Henner, J.J.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Avec des Assassins avec des Incendiaries avec des Voleurs, 1918 October; AFR0499; 16x11 inches (Box 35)
      - Alliance Universitaire. Vigilance; Souvenir, 1918; AFR0500; 20x26 inches (Box 35)
        Artist: Bompard, P.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Foch...., 1918; AFR0501; 47x64 inches (Box 36)
        Artist: Faria, Atelier. Place of Publication: France.
      - Pour l'Artisan de la Paix. Au President Wilson, 1918; AFR0502; 31x46 inches (Box 36)
      - La Banque de Mulhouse Recoit les Souscriptions, 1918 December; AFR0503; 32x11.5 inches (Box 36)
      - Les 'Quatre de l'Edition Francaise Illustree, 1915; AFR0504; 47x32 inches (Box 36)
        Artist: Bofa, Gus. Place of Publication: France.
      - L'Oeuvre Edite: 'Ce que Sera la Grande Paix; Par H.G. Wells., 1918; AFR0505; 32x47 inches (Box 36)
        Artist: Becan. Place of Publication: France.
      - Le Travail Force en Belgique, 1918; AFR0506; 21x30 inches (Box 36)
      - Lique Maritime Francaise, 1919 February; AFR0507; 31x47 inches (Box 36)
      - Laissez Circuler la Monnaie d'Argent et de Billion, 1918; AFR0508; 14x22 inches (Box 36)
        Artist: Grognuz, Beatrix. Place of Publication: France.
      - Fumeurs de l'Arriere Economisez le tabac pour que nos Soldats, 1918; AFR0509; 14x22 inches (Box 36)
        Artist: Menard, Andree. Place of Publication: France.
      - Le Permissionaire, 1917 May; AFR0510; 30x23 inches (Box 36)
        Artist: Guillaume. Place of Publication: France.
      - Rentree d'Orient, 1917 May; AFR0511; 39x29 inches (Box 36)
        Artist: Rabier, Benjamin. Place of Publication: France.
      - Au Reveil, 1917 May; AFR0512; 31x23 inches (Box 36)
      - La Statue de Strasbourg, 1918; AFR0513; 24x30 inches (Box 37)
        Artist: Galland, A.. Place of Publication: France.
      - Exposition Nationale a Strasbourg 19 juillet, 1919 July; AFR0514; 34x43 inches (Box 37)
        Artist: Gachot, Jacques. Place of Publication: France.
      - Exposition Nationale a Strasbourg, 1919 July; AFR0515; 28x37 inches (Box 37)
      - Jeux Inter-Allies, Stade Pershing, 1919 June; AFR0516; 31x47 inches (Box 37)
        Artist: Dulin, J.H.. Place of Publication: France.
      - S-Secretariat d'Etat a la Demobilisation, 1919; AFR0517; 23x31 inches (Box 37)
        Artist: Forain, Jean-Louis. Place of Publication: France.
      - On Est Prie de ne pas Gracher Par Terre., 1918; AFR0518; 19x12 inches (Box 37)
        Artist: Rouffe. Place of Publication: France.
      - La Ville de Lille a la Ville de Londres., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0519; 24x17 inches (Box 37)
      - L'Alarme, 1918; AFR0520; 13x20 inches (Box 37)
      - SAUVEGARDE - Avis est donne par L'AMBASSADEUR DES ETATS-UNIS, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0521; 25x15 inches (Box 37)
      - SCHUTZBRIEF - Die Botschaft der Vereinigten Staaten, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0522; 25x15 inches (Box 37)
      - Attendez un instant ca chauffe!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0523; 19x13 inches (Box 37)
      - Munissez vous de monnaie!, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0524; 19x13 inches (Box 37)
      - Pas Trop de chahut S.V.P., Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AFR0525; 19x13 inches (Box 37)
    - Great Britain
      - To My People, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0001; 40x60 inches (Box 38)
        Artist: Unknown. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - To My People, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0002; 20x30 inches (Box 38)
      - To My People, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0003; 20x30 inches (Box 38)
      - Public Warning, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0004; 23x34 inches (Box 38)
      - At the Court of Buckingham Palace, the 10th Day of May, 1916, 1916 May 10; AGB0005; 15x17 inches (Box 38)
      - Territorial Force, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0006; 14x17 inches (Box 38)
      - General Mobilization. Army Reserve, 1914 August; AGB0007; 16x20 inches (Box 38)
      - Police Notice. Air Raid Warning, 1917 November 7; AGB0008; 17x27 inches (Box 38)
      - City of Westminster. Air Raid Warnings, 1918 January; AGB0009; 15x20 inches (Box 38)
      - By the King. A Proclamation, 1917 April; AGB0010; 09x13 inches (Box 38)
      - G.R. War Service Badges and Certificates. Notice of Withdrawal, 1916 December 18; AGB0011; 30x40 inches (Box 38)
      - Public Notice. Defense of the Realm Regulations, 1918 May 23; AGB0012; 20x30 inches (Box 38)
      - Order. I, General the Right Honourable Sir J.G. Maxwell, K.C.B., 1916 September 28; AGB0013; 20x30 inches (Box 38)
      - Rules for the Use of Trinitrotoluene, 1917 February 19; AGB0014; 23x35 inches (Box 38)
      - England Expects Every Man to Do His Duty and Join the Army Today, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0015; 20x30 inches (Box 39)
      - Rally Round the Flag, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0016; 20x30 inches (Box 39)
      - Your King and Country Need You, 1914 November; AGB0017; 20x30 inches (Box 39)
      - Men of the Empire, to Arms, 1914 November; AGB0018; 20x30 inches (Box 39)
      - Your King and Country Need You, 1914 November; AGB0019; 20x30 inches (Box 39)
      - The Kaiser's Insult, 1914 October; AGB0020; 21x32 inches (Box 39)
      - Offer Your Services Now, 1914 November; AGB0021; 20x30 inches (Box 39)
      - The Scrap of Paper, 1914 October; AGB0022; 21x32 inches (Box 39)
      - A Call to Arms. Your Country Needs You Today, 1914 November; AGB0023; 10x30 inches (Box 39)
      - In Her Hour of Need Your Country Calls for You, 1914 November; AGB0024; 10x30 inches (Box 39)
      - Fight for King and Empire, 1914; AGB0025; 10x30 inches (Box 39)
      - Follow Me, Your Country Needs You, 1914 December; AGB0026; 20x30 inches (Box 40)
      - Fall in! Answer Now in Your Country's Hour of Need, 1914 November; AGB0027; 20x30 inches (Box 40)
      - Fall in! Answer Now in Your Country's Hour of Need, 1914 November; AGB0028; 60x50 inches (Box 40)
      - The Scrap of Paper, 1915 June; AGB0029; 20x30 inches (Box 40)
      - The Scrap of Paper (Welsh), 1914 December; AGB0030; 20x30 inches (Box 40)
      - Remember Belgium. Enlist Today, 1915 March; AGB0031; 30x40 inches (Box 40)
      - Your King and Country Need You, 1914; AGB0032; 20x30 inches (Box 40)
        Artist: Wood, Lawson. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - A Chip Off the Old Block, 1914; AGB0033; 20x30 inches (Box 40)
      - Remember Belgium, 1914 December; AGB0034; 15x20 inches (Box 40)
      - He Did His Duty, Will You Do Yours?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0035; 20x30 inches (Box 40)
      - He Did His Duty, Will You Do Yours?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0036; 20x30 inches (Box 41)
      - Another Call; More Men and Still More, 1914 December; AGB0037; 20x30 inches (Box 41)
      - Come Along, Boys, 1915 April; AGB0038; 20x30 inches (Box 41)
      - Come Along, Boys, 1914 December; AGB0039; 20x30 inches (Box 41)
      - Britons! Your Country Needs You, 1914 December; AGB0040; 20x30 inches (Box 41)
      - The Veteran's Farewell, 1914; AGB0041; 20x30 inches (Box 41)
        Artist: Dodd, Frank. Place of Publication: Great Britain.
      - A Happy New Year to Our Gallant Soldiers, 1914 December; 1915 January; AGB0042; 20x30 inches (Box 41)
      - Lend Your Strong Right Arm to Your Country. Enlist Now, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0043; 12x25 inches (Box 41)
      - Why Are You Stopping HERE When Your Pals Are Out THERE?, Circa 1914 - circa 1918; AGB0044; 06x30 inches (Box 41)